[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following tracks is not on the soundtrack of Team America: World Police?", "correct_answer": "Freedom Isnt Here", "incorrect_answers": ["Everyone Has AIDS", "America F**k Yeah", "Only a Woman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Indoor cats tend to live longer.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the literal translation of the Quechua word pachamanca, which refers to a traditional Native American dish?", "correct_answer": "Earthen pot", "incorrect_answers": ["Under the fire", "From the ground", "Hot stone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1908, this caricaturist, regarded as the father of French animation, made the film Fantasmagorie, which is considered the first fully-animated film ever made.", "correct_answer": "Emile Cohl", "incorrect_answers": ["Andr\u00e9 Gill", "None of these", "Patrice de Mac-Mahon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of these countries is showing negative facial expressions considered impolite and is therefore avoided?  Negative expressions are instead usually masked with smile or laughter.", "correct_answer": "Japan", "incorrect_answers": ["Peru", "Kenya", "Indonesia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to statistics from the past 3 decades of the 20th century, there is a significant drop in polar bears\u2019 size.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is Gold Leader in the Battle of Endor in Episode VI:  Return of the Jedi?", "correct_answer": "Lando Calrissian", "incorrect_answers": ["Luke Skywalker", "Han Solo", "Admiral Ackbar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The composition-dependant strategy works best in this kind of Blackjack game.", "correct_answer": "Single-deck", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Eight-deck", "Two-deck"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of shark is the scary man-eating monster in the 1975 horror movie Jaws directed by Steven Spielberg?", "correct_answer": "Great white shark", "incorrect_answers": ["Tiger shark", "Whale shark", "Grey shark"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these names belongs to the fox species that is the second smallest fox species in the world, slightly smaller than a domestic cat?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Short-Tailed Fox", "Coast Fox", "California Channel Island Fox"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What river encountered during the Lewis and Clark expedition (1804-1806) flows directly into the Pacific Ocean between Washington and Oregon?", "correct_answer": "Columbia", "incorrect_answers": ["Missouri", "Snake", "Colorado"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Some dinosaurs swam in the oceans.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]